<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<xml>

    <metadata>
        <title>Invincible</title>
        <creator>ROBERT KIRKMAN (CO-CREATOR, WRITER, LETTERER)Cory Walker( Co-Creator, Artist) Billl
            Crabtree(Colorist)</creator>
        <publisher>Jim Valentino(ImageComics)</publisher>
        <date>Apri 2003</date>
        <language>english</language>
        <issue num="3">Compendium 1</issue>
        <link>https://archive.org/details/invincible-compendiums/Invincible%2C%20Vol.%201/page/n51/mode/2up</link>
    </metadata>

    <comic>
        <page n="52">
            <panel p="1">
                <caption speaker="Mayor?">WE ARE CURRENTLY WORKING WITH THE AUTHORITIES TO GlVE THEM
                    ALL THE INFORMATION WE CAN IN ORDER TO HELP THEM LOCATE THE MISSING STUDENTS.
                    .</caption>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mayor">I MUST STRESS TO YOU ALL THAT THIS IS NOT A REASON TO
                    PANIC. THE THREE MISSING STUDENTS, THOUGH REPORTED MISSING ON DIFFERENT DAYS,
                    DID KNOW EACH OTHER. IT'S POSSIBLE THIS WAS PLANNED BY THEM AND NO FOUL PLAY HAS
                    TAKEN PLACE. STILL, WE CALLED THIS SCHOOL MEETING SO THAT THE RUMORS WOULDN'T
                    OVERWHELM THE TRUTH. YOU KNOW WHAT WE KNOW. JUST TO BE SAFE TRY NOT TO GO
                    ANYWHERE ALONE, AND PLEASE REPORT ANYTHING SUSPICIOUS TO EITHER ME OR ANY OF THE
                    OTHER PEOPLE YOU SEE HERE BESIDES ME.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Mayor">IF WE'RE LUCKY, THE MISSING STUDENTS WILL SHOW UP AND
                    EVERYTHING WILL GO BACK TO NORMAL, BUT UNTIL THEN KEEP YOUR EARS OPEN. IF ANY OF
                    YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS, I'LL BE IN MY OFFICE IN ABOUT FIFTEEN MINUTES AND MORE
                    THAN LIKELY FOR THE REST OF THE DAY. YOU CAN ALL GO BACK TO CLASS NOW. JUST GO
                    ON TO FOURTH PERIOD FROM HERE. PEOPLE WHO ARE ON FIRST LUNCH PERIOD CAN GO ON TO
                    THE CAFETERIA. THE BELL WILL RING IN SEVEN MINUTES, PLEASE BE WHERE YOU'RE
                    SUPPOSED TO BE BY THEN.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="53">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">EVERYONE'S THINKING IT... AND I'M GOING TO BE THE GUY TO
                    SAY IT. WHATEVER HAPPENED... COULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED TO A NICER BUNCH OF
                    GUYS.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">JESUS, MARK! THAT'S A PRETTY MEAN THING TO SAY! I TALKED TO
                    TODD A FEW TIMES... I MEAN, I CAN'T SPEAK FOR THE OTHER TWO BUT HE AT LEAST
                    SEEMED NICE.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">YOU'RE TOTALLY CLUELESS! WHY DO YOU THINK TODD JEFFERSON
                    WOULD BE NICE TO YOU? OFF THE TOP OF MY HEAD... I THINK IT MAY HAVE SOMETHING TO
                    DO WITH YOU BEING AN EXTREMELY ATTRACTIVE GIRL.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">YOU KNOW I'M DATING REX, RIGHT?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">WHOA, WHOA! THAT'S NOT WHERE I WAS GOING WITH THAT AT ALL!
                    ... HEH.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">RIIIGHT. SO, ARE YOU ON YOUR WAY TO THE CAFETERIA TOO, OR
                    ARE YOU JUST WALKING WITH ME?</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">WELL, I GUESS WE HAVE THE SAME LUNCH PERIOD, TOO. I CAN'T
                    BELIEVE WE HADN'T MET BEFORE LAST MONTH.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="54">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">IS THIS SEAT TAKEN?</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">NOT AT ALL. HAVE AT IT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">SORRY IF I MADE IT WEIRD BACK THERE. I JUST WANTED TO MAKE
                    SURE YOU DIDN'T THINK--</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT. IT DOESN'T NEED TO BE BROUGHT UP
                    AGAIN.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <action>Mark and Eve sit in silence.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <action>Mark and Eve sit in silence.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">SO... SURE IS FUN BEING A SUPER-HERO, ISN'T IT?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="7">
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">DID YOU HEAR THERE WAS ANOTHER MALL BOMBING? ROBOT IS TRYING
                    TO FIGURE OUT WHO'S BEHIND THEM, BUT THE BOMBS ARE SO POWERFUL THEY ARE
                    DISINTEGRATING ALL THE EVIDENCE AT THE SCENE.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="8">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">ANOTHER BOMBING? THAT'S TWO IN LESS THAN THREE
                    WEEKS.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="55">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">IF YOU WANT TO SWING BY THE... "SECRET LAIR" (OR WHATEVER
                    THE BOYS CALL IT) AFTER SCHOOL TODAY, I'M SURE ROBOT WOULD BE GLAD TO SEE YOU.
                    YOU NEVER DID GET BACK TO HIM ON WHETHER OR NOT YOU WERE GOING TO JOIN THE
                    TEAM.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN MAKE IT. I'VE GOT TO WORK
                    TONIGHT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">YOU STILL WORK AT THE BURGER MART? ISN'T YOUR DAD A
                    SEMI-FAMOUS NOVELIST?!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">WELL.. YEAH, I MEAN... IT'S NOT LIKE I NEED THE MONEY, HE
                    MAKES ME WORK THERE BECAUSE HE THINKS IT BUILDS CHARACTER.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">WEIRD. WELL, I'VE GOT TO GET TO CLASS. SEE YOU
                    AROUND.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">LATER.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="William">SO, THE RUMORS ARE TRUE. YOU GUYS ARE GOING
                    OUT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">OH. HEY, WILLIAM... GOING OUT WHERE?</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="William">DON'T PLAY DUMB WITH ME. YOU TWO ARE AN ITEM, BOYFRIEND
                    AND GIRLFRIEND, AND ALL THE PERKS THAT COME WITH IT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="7">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">TRUST ME. SHE'S NOT MY GIRLFRIEND.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="56">
            <panel p="1">
                <action>The sign outside for Burger Mart is shown.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <action>Mark is shown in the kicthen looking distressed.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Dan">GRAYSON! FRIES! WE GOT CUSTOMERS WAITING!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">COMING RIGHT UP, SIR!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Dan">COMING RIGHT UP? DO YOU REALIZE HOW LONG OUR CUSTOMERS HAVE
                    BEEN WAITING?! DON'T YOU KNOW THAT WAITING CUSTOMERS AREN'T HAPPY
                    CUSTOMERS?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">NO... I GUESS NOT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="57">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Dan">YOU GUESS?!??! WELL, YOU BETTER HOPE COME FRIDAY THAT I
                    GUESS THAT YOU SHOULD GET PAID! NOW, GO TAKE OUT THE TRASH. I'LL FINISH THE
                    FRIES!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">YOU KNOW WHAT? I THINK I'LL JUST QUIT INSTEAD!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">JERK!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <action>Mark is standing outside of Burger Mart after quitting.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">DAD'S GOING TO KILL ME.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="58">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">BOY, THAT CASSEROLE SURE WAS GOOD, MOM.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">ABSOLUTELY, HON'. YOU REALLY OUTDID YOURSELF
                    TONIGHT.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Debbie">THANKS, BUT YOU'RE BOTH STILL GOING TO HAVE TO DO THE
                    DISHES.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">CURSES... FOILED AGAIN.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">SO, HOW WAS WORK TODAY?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">OH! FINE! DO YOU WANT TO WASH OR RINSE!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">OH, I'LL BE WASHING, TONIGHT. HOW MANY DISHES DID I HAVE
                    TO HAND BACK TO YOU LAST NIGHT?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">I WAS THINKING... NOW THAT YOU'RE AN ACTIVE SUPER-HERO,
                    YOU'VE GOT MORE IMPORTANT THINGS TO DO THAN FLIP BURGERS. I DON'T SEE ANY REASON
                    WHY YOU CAN'T JUST QUIT. IT'S NOT LIKE YOU EVER REALLY NEEDED THE
                    MONEY.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="7">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">I THINK I COULD MANAGE THAT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
    </comic>




</xml>
