<Issue2>
    <page type="1">
        <Omniman>
            <p type="1">Okay son, you may have noticed by now that I'm not like normal dads. I've...
                    <bold>avoided</bold> the subject for far too many years, and your mother and I
                have decided that it's time you knew the truth.</p>
            <p>We think you're old enough for me to tell you where I <bold>really</bold> come
                from.</p>
        </Omniman>

    </page>


    <page type="2">
        <char name="Omniman" type="narrator">
            <panel type="1">
                <p type="1"> Millions of miles from here, out in deep space, is the planet Viltrum,
                    a cool blue oasis alone in a solar system much like our own.</p>
                <p type="2">I was born on this planet</p>
            </panel>
            <panel type="2">
                <p type="1"> Its people are not completely unlike humans, although, they and I, have
                    abilities in addition to what humans have. We can fly, move at super-speed, and
                    possess great strength... by human standards.</p>

                <p type="2"> Viltrum was a planet that had achieved a perfect global society. There
                    was no illness, no murder, no war, it was a relative utopia.</p>
            </panel>
            <panel type="3">
                <p type="1"> With no conflict at hand, our high council refused to let our society
                    become complacent.</p>
            </panel>
            <panel type="4">
                <p type="1">Council memebers argued that rather than revel in our newfound
                    perfection, we should take it upon ourselves to ensure that other races, lesser
                    developed than our own, should be allowed to develop to our level of
                    advancement.</p>
            </panel>
            <panel type="5">
                <p type="1"> It was agreed upon unanimously.</p>
            </panel>
        </char>
    </page>

       

            <page type="3">


                <panel type="1">
                    <p type="1"> Shortly after the high council had approved the idea, the world
                        betterment committee was formed.</p>
                </panel>
                <panel type="2">
                    <p type="1"> The first step of the initiative was to locate other plaets that
                        were in a cruical stage of development...</p>
                    <p type="2">... Planets that were far enough along that the possibility of
                        greatness was there, but were not so far along that their outcome was
                        already decided.</p>
                </panel>
                <panel type="3">
                    <p type="1"> The second step was to install global defense systems to protect
                        the planet from spaceborne menaces, both natural and unnatural, that might
                        prevent the survival of the civilization.</p>
                </panel>
                <panel type="4">
                    <p type="1"> The final step was to send a team of scientists down to the
                        planet's surface to assist in the advancement of the civilization's
                        technologies.</p>
                    <p type="2"> This team would stay behind on the planet, monitoring its
                        progress.</p>
                </panel>


            </page>

            <page type="4">
                <panel type="1">
                    <p type="1"> Word traveled around our planet about how much food the world
                        betterment committee was doing. Soon, it was the most popular profession on
                        Viltrum.</p>
                </panel>

                <panel type="2">
                    <p type="1"> Of course, when I came of age, I signed up for duty. I was on the
                        search committee; my job was to locate and suggest planets that might be
                        eligible for our interference.</p>
                    <p type="2"> By then, the operation had been expanded and perfected. I was
                        stationed on a mobile base that traveled from planet to planet as we
                        discovered them.</p>
                </panel>

                <panel type="3">
                    <p type="1"> I was in my third year of service when I discovered Earth. I
                        convinced the committee to do a physical inspection of the planet.</p>
                    <p type="2"> During the long journey to Earth, I used our long range sensors to
                        study the planet and the civilization that lived there.</p>
                </panel>

                <panel type="4">
                    <p type="1"> By the time we arrived, I had grown fond of Earth and the people on
                        it. Iwas fascinated by the achievements that had accomplished in such a
                        short time.</p>
                    <p type="2"> I pleaded for authorization to add Earth to our betterment
                        schedule, but it was deemed too crude and not developed enough for our
                        interference.</p>
                </panel>

                <panel type="5">
                    <p type="1"> I refused to give up, and offered an alternative solution. I
                        volunteered to relocate to Earth, and be its sole protector, dedicated to
                        the survival of its civilization.</p>
                    <p type="2"> Due to Earth's location in such a remote area of the universe, I
                        was warned that there might not be any chance of returning.</p>
                </panel>

                <panel type="6">
                    <p type="1"> I went anyway.</p>
                </panel>
            </page>
            <page type="5">
                <panel type="1">
                    <p type="1"> No amount of research could have prepared me for what I would
                        experience upon my arrival.</p>
                </panel>
                <panel type="2">
                    <p type="1">Earth was a vibrant nest of individuality. I marveled at the people
                        I saw as they scurried about their daily lives.</p>
                </panel>
                <panel type="3">
                    <p type="1"> It was there, anound the people, that I instantly knew I had made
                        the right choice.</p>
                    <p type="2"> I might have even forgotten what my mission on Earth was...</p>
                </panel>
                <panel type="4">
                    <p type="1">...Had I not been so abruptly reminded.</p>
                </panel>
                <panel type="5">
                    <p type="1"> With my mission clearly at hand, I went to work.</p>
                </panel>
                <panel type="6">
                    <p type="1"> The people of Earth needed someone to keep them safe...</p>
                </panel>
                <panel type="7">
                    <p type="1">...And I was here to protect them.</p>
                </panel>
                <panel type="8">
                    <p type="1"> It was less than a year before I met your mother... but that's a
                        story for another time.</p>
                </panel>


            </page>

      

        <page type="6">
            <Omniman type="speech">
                <panel type="1">
                    <p type="1"> I know this a lot to take in at one time, but you're old enough to
                        know the truth. And unfortunately... I'm not dont yet. On top of all this...
                        there's more. </p>
                    <p type="2">You see, you're getting older, son...</p>
                </panel>
                <panel type="2">
                    <p type="1"> ...Things are going to start to change for you in a few years as
                        you hit puberty. </p>
                    <p type="2"> You're going to start to get acne. </p>
                    <p type="3"> Your voice will start to crack and eventually change. </p>
                    <p type="4"> You'll begin to grow hair in strange and new places.</p>
                    <p type="5"> You're goig to start looking at girls in a whole new light.</p>
                </panel>
                <panel type="3"> There's a good chance that you're going to start to develop super
                    powers.</panel>
            </Omniman>
        </page>

    

    <page type="7">
        <Omniman type="Speech">
            <panel type="1">
                <p type="1"> Super-strength, super-speed, flight... the whole bit.</p>
                <p type="2">All the powers <bold>I</bold> have.</p>
                <p type="3">...</p>
                <p type="4">Mark? Do you understand?</p>
            </panel>
        </Omniman>
        <panel type="2"/>
        <panel type="3"/>
        <panel type="4">
            <Mark type="speech">...</Mark>
        </panel>
        <panel type="5">
            <Mark type="speech">
                <p type="1"> Wow.</p>
                <p type="2"> Im going to be able to fly?!</p>
            </Mark>
        </panel>

    </page>

    <page type="8">
        <Mark type="speech">
            <panel type="1">
                <p type="1"> Yeah...</p>
            </panel>
            <panel type="2">
                <p type="1"> I can fly... </p>
            </panel>
            <panel type="3"/>
            <panel type="4"> *sigh* </panel>
            <panel type="5"> Screw this. </panel>
        </Mark>
    </page>
    <page type="9">
        <Mark>
            <panel type="1"/>
            <panel type="2"/>
            <panel type="3"/>
            <panel type="4"/>
            <panel type="5"/>
            <panel type="6">
                <Mark type="speech">
                    <p type="1"> What the--?!</p>
                </Mark>
            </panel>
        </Mark>
    </page>
    <page type="10">
        <panel type="1">
            <Mark type="speech"> Is he stealing...<bold> game boxes?</bold></Mark>
        </panel>
        <panel type="2">
            <MaulerBrother type="1"> Eh?</MaulerBrother>
        </panel>
    </page>
    <page type="11">
        <panel type="1">
            <MaulerBrother>
                <p type="1"> Back off!</p>
            </MaulerBrother>
        </panel>
        <panel type="2"/>
        <panel type="3">
            <MaulerBrother>
                <p> Aren't you out a little past you betime, young man?</p>
            </MaulerBrother>
        </panel>
        <panel type="4">
            <Mark>
                <p type="1">Actually...yeah.</p>
            </Mark>
        </panel>
        <panel type="5"/>
        <panel type="6"/>
    </page>
    <page type="12">
        <panel type="1">
            <Rex type="speech">
                <p type="1">That was a BB, you dont want to see what I can do with a golf ball.</p>
                <p type="2"> Now.</p>
                <p type="3"> Who started it?</p>
            </Rex>
        </panel>
    </page>
    <page type="13">
        <panel type="1">
            <MaulerBrother type="speech">
                <p type="1"> I'll give you one guess.</p>
            </MaulerBrother>
        </panel>
        <panel type="2">Skra-BOOM!</panel>
        <panel type="3">
            <Robot type="speech">
                <p type="1">Way to go, Rex. We <bold>had</bold> the element of surprise.</p>
            </Robot>
            <Rex type="speech">
                <p type="1"> Sorry, 'Bot. It seemed like a good idea at the time.</p>
            </Rex>
            <Robot type="speech">
                <p type="2"> Well, try to leave the good ideas up to me.</p>
            </Robot>
        </panel>
        <panel type="4">
            <Robot>
                <p type="1"> And, um...</p>
                <p type="2">...We're going to need one real soon.</p>
            </Robot>
        </panel>
        <panel type="5"/>
        <MaulerBrother type="speech">
            <p type="1"> You got that right!</p>
        </MaulerBrother>
        <panel type="6">Krok!</panel>
    </page>

    <page type="14">
        <panel type="1">
            <Robot type="speech">
                <p type="1"> Wow.</p>
                <p type="2">Never mind. Nice job, kid.</p>
            </Robot>
        </panel>
        <panel type="2">
            <Robot type="speech">
                <p type="1"> I'll have another vehicle sent to us by remote. Kate, pull our friend,
                    Mauler out of the way so we won't attract too much attention.</p>
            </Robot>
        </panel>
        <panel type="3">
            <AtomEve type="speech">
                <p type="1"> Nice costume, man</p>
            </AtomEve>
            <Mark type="speech">
                <p type="1"> Sorry, there wasn;t a phone booth handy.</p>
                <p type="2">Um...Do I know you?</p>
            </Mark>
        </panel>
        <panel type="4">
            <AtomEve type="speech">
                <p type="1">You know... You <bold>do</bold> look familiar... </p>
            </AtomEve>
        </panel>
        <panel type="5">
            <Robot type="speech">
                <p type="1"> Well, our ride's here, but I can see that a brief introduction is
                    needed before we depart.</p>
                <p type="2"> We're the teen team. I'm <bold>Robot.</bold></p>
                <p type="3"> You've met <bold> Atom Eve.</bold></p>
                <p type="4"> That's <bold> Rex Splode.</bold></p>
                <p type="5">With <bold>Dupli-Kate</bold> rounding out the team.</p>
                <p type="6">And you?</p>
            </Robot>
            <Mark type="speech">
                <p type="1">I'm M-- I mean, Invincible.</p>
            </Mark>
            <Robot type="speech">
                <p type="7">
                    <bold> Cute.</bold>
                </p>
            </Robot>
        </panel>
        <panel type="6">
            <Mark type="speech">
                <p type="1"> Nice to meet you.</p>
            </Mark>
            <AtomEve type="speech">
                <p type="1"> See you around</p>
            </AtomEve>
        </panel>
    </page>

    <page type="15">
        <panel type="1">
            <Mark type="speech">
                <p type="1"> Hah!</p>
                <p type="2"> I knew it.</p>
            </Mark>
        </panel>
        <panel type="2">
            <AtomEve type="speech">
                <p type="1">Hey, it's <bold>YOU!</bold> We've been in biology together all this
                    time...</p>
                <p type="2"> Mark, right?</p>
            </AtomEve>
        </panel>
        <panel type="3">
            <Mark type="speech">
                <p type="1">Yeah. Um, is there any way you can keep this to yourself? You never know
                    when one of your teammates is going to crazy and become the next big
                    villain.</p>
            </Mark>
            <AtomEve type="speech">
                <p type="1"> Oh, that only happens in comic books.</p>
            </AtomEve>
        </panel>
        <panel type="4">
            <Mark type="speech">
                <p type="1"> It's always better to play it sa--</p>
                <p type="2">*Yawn*</p>
            </Mark>
        </panel>
        <panel type="5">
            <Mark type="speech">
                <p type="1">Sorry about all that... I'm not used to these late nights...</p>
                <p type="2">*I'm still new to this... I just hit two months.</p>
            </Mark>
        </panel>
        <panel type="6">
            <AtomEve type="speech">
                <p type="1"> You'll get the hang of it. Teen superheroes sart drinking coffee at an
                    early age.</p>
            </AtomEve>
        </panel>
    </page>

    <page type="16">
        <panel type="1">
            <AtomEve type="speech">
                <p type="1"> Listen, we're following up on the incident from last night today.
                    You're welcome to tage along if you'd like.</p>
            </AtomEve>
            <Mark type="speech">
                <p type="1"> Id'love to.</p>
            </Mark>
        </panel>
        <panel type="2">
            <Mark type="speech">
                <p type="1">Why are we going out here? Do you take the bus to your team's secret
                    base?</p>
            </Mark>
        </panel>
        <panel type="3">
            <AtomEve type="speech">
                <p type="1">Are you kidding me? I can fly!</p>
            </AtomEve>
        </panel>
        <panel type="4">
            <AtomEve type="speech">
                <p type="1"> C'mon. We can change back there.</p>
            </AtomEve>
        </panel>
        <panel type="5">
            <Mark type="speech">
                <p type="1"> So... you come here often?</p>
            </Mark>
            <AtomEve type="speech">
                <p type="1"> Every day.</p>
            </AtomEve>
            <Mark type="speech"><p type="2"> Nice place.</p>></Mark>
        </panel>
        <panel type="6"> <AtomEve type="speech"><p type="1"> Do you know of any other secluded placse around here?</p><p type="2">Wow. That was quick.</p></AtomEve> <Mark type="speech"><p type="1">Thanks.</p><p type="2">I guess notm but now that we're in costume... how do we get out of here without being spotted?</p></Mark></panel>
        <panel type="7"><AtomEve type="speech"> <p type="1"> You'd be surprised how rarely people ever look up.</p></AtomEve></panel>
    </page>

    <page type="17">
        <panel type="1"><Mark type="speech"> <p type="1"></p></Mark><Robot type="speech"><bold> You're late.</bold> I'll assume that's our new friend from last night with you...<p type="1"></p></Robot></panel>
        <panel type="2"><Robot type="speech"><p type="1">Good. Oh, and he's wearing a much nicer costume. Kate and rex are out on another mission, he'll be good use tonight.</p></Robot></panel>
        <panel type="3"><Robot type="speech"><p type="1">Speaking of which, if you had gotten here three minutes later I would have had to do this alone.</p><p type="2">C'mon.</p></Robot></panel>
        <panel type="4"><Robot type="speech"><p type="1">I erased mauler's memories from last night, and left him close to the toy store he robbed. He'll be disoriented and will more than likely seek out familiar ground.</p><p type="2">My hypothesis is that he will lead us to his base and we'll be able to figure out what his plans for the video game systems were.</p></Robot></panel>
        <panel type="5"><Robot type="speech"><p type="1">I've been tracking him from here, but we need to be on site when he arrives.</p><p type="2"> I was afraid I was going to have to leave without you.</p></Robot></panel>
        <panel type="6"><Mark type="speech"><p type="1">Sorry about that.</p></Mark><Robot type="speech"><p type="1">Don't worry about it... I'm not even sure I'll need you.</p></Robot></panel>
    </page>

    <page type="18">
        <panel type="1">
            <Robot type="speech">
                <p type="1">There he is.</p>
            </Robot>
        </panel>
        <panel type="2">
            <MaulerBrother type="speech">
                <p type="1">...</p>
            </MaulerBrother>
        </panel>
        <panel type="3">
            <MaulerBrother type="speech">
                <p type="1">Where have you been? We need those processors! We're not going to have
                    enough to power the robots without that ned shipment.</p>
            </MaulerBrother>
        </panel>
        <panel type="4">
            <MaulerBrother type="speech">
                <p type="1"> I don't know what happened. All last night is a blur. I remember going
                    out to get the new shipment at the Toys B' We... and then... nothing.</p>
                <p type="2">So I came back.</p>
            </MaulerBrother>
        </panel>
        <panel type="5">
            <MaulerBrother type="speech">
                <p type="1"> I don't think you realize how important our work here is. We badly need
                    those extra processors. That shipment is already in stock by now, and they
                    wont't be receiving another for nearly a month. </p>
            </MaulerBrother>
        </panel>
        <panel type="6">
            <MaulerBrother type="speech">
                <p type="1"> I'm not sure our plans can wait that long.</p>
            </MaulerBrother>
        </panel>
    </page>

    <page type="19">
        <panel type="1">
            <Unknown>
                <p type="1"> I think we've heard enough.</p>
            </Unknown>
        </panel>
        <panel type="2">
            <Robot type="speech">
                <p type="1"> Keep the other one from activating the robots, I'll deal with this
                    one!</p>
            </Robot>
        </panel>
        <panel type="3">
            <MaulerBrother type="speech">
                <p type="1">What makes you think we need the robots to defeat you?</p>
            </MaulerBrother>
        </panel>
        <panel type="4">
            <AtomEve type="speech">
                <p type="1">Let go!</p>
            </AtomEve>
        </panel>

    </page>

    <page type="20">
        <panel type="1">
            <MaulerBrother type="speech">
                <p type="1"> I don't know what you hope to accomplish here. You're obviously in over
                    your head!</p>
            </MaulerBrother>
        </panel>
        <panel type="2">
            <Robot type="speech">
                <p type="1"> You're obviously not paying attention.</p>
            </Robot>
        </panel>
        <panel type="3"/>
        <panel type="4">
            <MaulerBrother type="speech">
                <p type="1"> It...will..take more...than... </p>
                <p type="2">...</p>
                <p type="3"> That...</p>
            </MaulerBrother>
        </panel>
        <panel type="5">
            <Robot type="speech">
                <p type="1"> I'll see what I can do.</p>
            </Robot>
        </panel>
        <panel type="6">
            <Robot>
                <p type="1"> Thanks for the help, Invincible!</p>
                <p type="2"> You seem to be a pretty useful guy. Think you might be interested in
                    staying with us?</p>
            </Robot>
        </panel>
        <panel type="7">
            <Mark type="speech">
                <p type="1"> I'll think about it</p>
                <p type="2"> Is it always this easy?</p>
            </Mark>
        </panel>
    </page>

    <page type="21">
        <panel type="1"/>
        <panel type="2"/>
        <panel type="3"/>
        <Man type="speech">
            <panel type="4">
                <p type="">*Yawn*</p>
            </panel>
            <panel type="5">
                <p type="1">Where am I?</p>
            </panel>
            <panel type="6">
                <p type="1">What the--?!</p>
            </panel>
        </Man>
    </page>


    <page type="22">
        <panel type="1"> BOOM!</panel>
    </page>
</Issue2>
