<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>

    <metadata>
        <title>Invincible</title>
        <creator>ROBERT KIRKMAN (CO-CREATOR, WRITER, LETTERER)Cory Walker( Co-Creator, Artist) Billl
            Crabtree(Colorist)</creator>
        <publisher>Jim Valentino(ImageComics)</publisher>
        <date>Apri 2003</date>
        <language>english</language>
        <issue n="4">issue 4</issue>
        <link>https://archive.org/details/20210523_20210523_0901/Invincible%20004%20%282003%29%20%28digital%29%20%28Minutemen-InnerDemons%29/page/n2/mode/1up</link>
    </metadata>

    <comic>
        <page n="3">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="robot">REMARKABLE. THE GAME BOX PROCESSOR IS SO ADVANCED IT COULD
                    OPERATE THIS MACHINE FOR YEARS WITH A BUROUT RATE OF LESS THAN TEN PERCENT! HAD
                    WE NOT STOPPED THE MAULER TWINS BEFORE THEY ACTIVATED THEM THEY WOULD HAVE BEEN
                    NEARLY UNSTOPPABLE. FASCINATING. SIMPLY FASCINATING.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Invincible">ROBOT?</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="4">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="robot">HELLO, INVINCIBLE. WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Invincible">I'M TRYING TO FIND EVE... DO YOU KNOW WHERE SHE
                    IS?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="robot">EVE AND REX ARE OUT ON A MISSION RIGHT NOW, BUT THEY
                    SHOULD BE CHECKING IN HERE BEFORE THEY GO HOME FOR THE NIGHT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Invincible">CRAP... I REALLY NEED TO TALK TO HER.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="robot">WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO GIVE HER A MESSAGE? WAIT A MINUTE YOU
                    KNOW SHE'S DATING REX, RIGHT?</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Invincible"><bold>YEAH</bold>. ...THAT'S <bold>NOT</bold> WHAT
                    THIS IS ABOUT AT ALL. </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Invincible">IT'S THESE MALL BOMBINGS. UM... WELL... THIS IS GOING
                    TO SOUND WEIRD, BUT... SOMEONE IS TURNING KIDS FROM OUR SCHOOL INTO HUMAN
                    BOMB.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="robot">I KNOW.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="5">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="robot">Hello, Invincible. What can I do for you?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Invincible"> I’m trying to find Eve... Do you know where she is?
                </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Robot"> Eve and Rex went out on a mission right now. But she
                    should be checking in here before too long. She might be home for the
                    night.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Invincible"> Crap... I really need to talk to her. </dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Robot"> Would you like me to give her a message? </dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Robot"> Wait a minute, you know she's dating rex, right? </dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Invincible"> Yeah. That’s not what this is about at
                    all.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Invincible"> It’s these mall bombings, man. While this is going
                    to sound weird... someone’s turning kids into human bombs. </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Robot">I know.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="6">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Invincible"> I mean, it’s late and all but I just wanted to let
                    her know so that— wait what? </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Robot"> Residue found at the blast sites indicated that the
                    timing mechanisms in all the bombs were organic in nature. More than likely,
                    human circulatory systems provided the catalyst. From that, it was merely
                    process of elimination to determine the age and relation of the humans that are
                    being used as bombs. I didn’t know they were all from your school in particular,
                    but I’m sure I would have... eventually. </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Invincible"> Well... I’m only sure that the most recent one went
                    to my school, but he's one of the three kids that are missing. </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Eve"> Well, if it isn’t our new pal, Invincible what are you
                    doing here? </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Invincible"> I think the mall bombing are connected to the
                    missing kids at our school. </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Rex">Oh, god, that’s awful.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Rex">Bye, babe.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Rex">*smeck*</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">Any idea who’s behind it?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="7">
                <dialogue speaker="Robot"> No, and there’s nothing we can do about that tonight. I
                    suggest you two go home and get some sleep. Then keep your eyes open at school
                    tomorrow. I’ll let you know if I figure out anything on my own. </dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
    </comic>




</xml>
